Vladimer karosanidze

AI + Software Engineer

<u>Jwdev080@gmail.com</u> / https://t.me/jwdev080/ Gabriel salosi 35

ABOUT ME

I have been working as a programmer for over 10 years and have been involved in over 50 projects.

The largest of these was the development of an AI-based attendance management system and time recorder terminal system.

As one of the main programmers in a team of 14 members, I was involved in the development and maintenance of various forms of the system, which included attendance management functions and a SHIFT auto-creation engine.

I was also able to gain valuable experience in emergency response to bugs that were discovered after release.

I am confident in the breadth of my programming skills.

I have knowledge in Deep Learning, Machine Learning, Computer Vision, Python, Django, React and C++, so I can handle a wide range of tasks.

I am also currently self-taught in Golang and will continue to learn other programming languages as the situation demands.

EXPERIENCE

DEC 2022 – SENIOR AI ENGINEER, Upwork.com · Freelancer

- Worked as a senior AI engineer, focused developing Python, Django, React.js projects.
- Developed over 30 models for data processing with Deep Learning, ML such as OCR, OMR, coin prediction, and object classification.
- Implemented importing resources from various kinds of databases like PostgreSQL, MongoDB, etc.
- Set up docker infrastructure for the back-end projects
- Worked as a senior DL engineer, I had developed the face swap project.

Technologies: Deep Learning, Machine Learning, Natural Language Processing, Computer Vision, Python, Django with Restful API, React, PostgreSQL

JUL 2020 – DEC 2022 SENIOR FULLSTACK ENGINEER,

- Worked as a senior software engineer with Django and React.js for front-end development and Django for back-end development.
- Collaborated with the product owner, marketing team, and designer to clarify requirements.
- Customized Bootstrap variables and configurations based on designer's style guide.
- Developed a Blood Bank website backend using Django.
- Developed a Student Attendance rate Management project.
- Worked as a senior computer vision engineer as the virtual ring environment project,
- car speed and condition monitoring program on the highway, and so on.
- Use the Elastic Search engine to improve the backend solution.

Technologies: Machine learning, Computer Vision, Medical image processing, NLP, OpenAI, React.js.

SEP 2017 – JUN 2020

JUNIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER, New Delhi, Delhi, India

- Worked as a junior python developer, focused developing the GUI design, algorithm implement, data processing, and so on.
- Set up the testing environment with Jest and Enzyme in the front-end and ensured it was stable with over 90% test coverage.
- Worked as a senior backend engineer, focused developing the data processing, with python, Django, flask.

Technologies: Python, Django, Flask, TypeScript, image processing, NLP, sound processing

AUG 2020 - DEC 2022

SOFTWARE APPLICATION DEVELOPER, AEE Oversea Technology· Student Internship & Contract

- Developed the Blood Bank Website sandiegobloodbank.org/.
- Developed 2 ai web site with NDA signature.

Technologies: C++, C#, Serial Communications, MFC, Data Processing, Reverse Engineering

EDUCATION

MAY 2011 - MAY 2016

Bachelor's Degree Science, University of Georgia

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Deep learning
- Machine learning
- Computer vision
- Image processing
- Audio processing
- NLP
- OpenAl API intergraing

- Python
- Django
- Flask
- React.js
- Algorithm